{
    "subject": "resource/Formica_japonica",
    "predicate": "property/hasPhotoCollection",
    "object": "http://wifo5-03.informatik.uni-mannheim.de/flickrwrappr/photos/Formica_japonica",
    "human_readable": "Formica japonica has a photo collection.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9695414304733276,
            "question": "Does Formica japonica have a visual collection?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.962208092212677,
            "question": "What does it suggest about Formica japonica that it has a photo collection?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9512497186660767,
            "question": "How might Formica japonica use its photo collection?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9485743045806885,
            "question": "Can you describe the types of photos in Formica japonica's collection?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9384670853614807,
            "question": "Is Formica japonica known for its collection?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8993207812309265,
            "question": "What kind of collection does Formica japonica possess?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8702869415283203,
            "question": "Formica japonica's collection - what can it be used for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8505989909172058,
            "question": "What is the nature of Formica japonica's collection?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.841020941734314,
            "question": "What does Formica japonica have?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6750991344451904,
            "question": "What is special about Formica japonica's collection compared to other species?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Formica japonica has a photo collection.",
            "html": "dbpedia_4292_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What does Formica japonica have?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4292_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the nature of Formica japonica's collection?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4292_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Formica japonica's collection - what can it be used for?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4292_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4292_16.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4292_23.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4292_28.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4292_3.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4292_34.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4292_37.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4292_48.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4292_49.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4292_69.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4292_79.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "Here is the response in the structured JSON format:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation: The documents provided do not contain any information about Formica japonica having a photo collection. However, they do mention that there are no other images of this species yet and provide an opportunity to upload photos. But it does not explicitly state that there is a photo collection associated with Formica japonica."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation: The documents mention multiple images related to Formica japonica, indicating that there is indeed a photo collection for this species."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": " {\n      \"output\": \"no\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": true,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'no'}\n\nThe provided documents do not support the statement that \"Formica japonica has a photo collection.\" While there is mention of an image related to Formica japonica (file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_4292/re-ranker-msmarco/48.txt), it does not indicate that there is a photo collection for the species. The documents suggest only one image provided by a contributor, and no indication of multiple photos or a collection is given."
        },
        "llama3.1:70b": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        }
    },
    "final_decision": -1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "mistral": {
            "reason": "There is no information provided suggesting that there is a collection of photos for Formica japonica. Instead, the text indicates that currently there are no other images of this species yet available to upload.",
            "category": 2
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "reason": "There are no other images of this species yet.",
            "category": 2
        }
    }
}